export default class Question3 {
  public static question: Question3[] = [
    {
      question: 'How can you verify the legitimacy of an email sender?',
      answers: [
        'A Click on any links provided in the email',
        'B Check the sender email address for authenticity',
        'C Respond to the email with personal information',
        'D Forward the email to friends for confirmation',
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'B Check the sender email address for authenticity',
      explanation: 'Check the sender email address for authenticity',
    },
    {
      question: 'What is a common sign of a phishing email?',
      answers: [
        'A Personalized greetings using your name',
        'B Urgent requests for immediate action',
        'C Clear and professional formatting',
        'D Inclusion of legitimate contact information'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'B Urgent requests for immediate action',
      explanation: 'Urgent requests for immediate action',
    },
    {
      question: 'What should you do if you receive an unexpected email requesting sensitive information?',
      answers: [
        'A Provide the requested information to verify your identity',
        'B Ignore the email and mark it as spam',
        'C Share the email on social media for advice',
        'D Reply with a request for more information about the sender'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'B Ignore the email and mark it as spam',
      explanation: 'Ignore the email and mark it as spam',
    },
    {
      question: 'How can you verify the safety of a link before clicking on it?',
      answers: [
        'A Click on the link and check the website for legitimacy',
        'B Hover over the link to preview the destination URL',
        'C Share the link on social media for feedback',
        'D Trust links that promise exclusive deals and discounts'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'B Hover over the link to preview the destination URL',
      explanation: 'Hover over the link to preview the destination URL',
    },
    {
      question: 'What is the significance of "https://" in a website URL?',
      answers: [
        'A It indicates a highly discounted website',
        'B It signifies a secure and encrypted connection',
        'C It means the website has fast loading times',
        'D It suggests the website is exclusive and trustworthy'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'B It signifies a secure and encrypted connection',
      explanation: 'It signifies a secure and encrypted connection',
    },
    {
      question: 'What should you look for in the address bar to ensure a website is secure?',
      answers: [
        'A An absence of any symbols or icons',
        'B A green padlock icon and "https://" at the beginning of the URL',
        'C A red warning sign indicating excitement',
        'D A blue checkmark next to the website name'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'A green padlock icon and "https://" at the beginning of the URL',
      explanation: 'green padlock icon and "https://" at the beginning of the URL',
    },
    {
      question: 'Why is it important to verify the authenticity of a website before entering personal information?',
      answers: [
        'A To increase the websites popularity',
        'B To avoid encountering interesting content',
        'C To prevent unauthorized access and data theft',
        'D To test the effectiveness of your antivirus software'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'C To prevent unauthorized access and data theft',
      explanation: 'To prevent unauthorized access and data theft',
    },
    {
      question: 'Why is it important to review a websites privacy policy before providing personal information?',
      answers: [
        'A To check the websites popularity',
        'B To understand how the website will handle and protect your data',
        'C To speed up the websites loading times',
        'D To verify the websites encryption level'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'B To understand how the website will handle and protect your data',
      explanation: 'To understand how the website will handle and protect your data',
    },
    {
      question: 'What should you do if you receive an email with a link claiming to be from a familiar organization?',
      answers: [
        'A Click on the link to confirm its authenticity',
        'B Forward the email to all your contacts for verification',
        'C Contact the organization directly using official contact information',
        'D Ignore the email without further investigation'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'C Contact the organization directly using official contact information',
      explanation: 'Contact the organization directly using official contact information',
    },
    {
      question: 'Your online friend asks you to send the photo of your identity card. What do you do?',
      answers: [
        'A You send a picture of your identity card',
        'B You do not send your identity card',
        'C You send them a photograph of you',
        'D You send a picture of your grandma'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'B You do not send your identity card',
      explanation: 'You do not send your identity card',
    },
    {
      question: 'You get an email asking for your house address in order to deliver some prize to you. What do you do?',
      answers: [
        'A You give them the address, because there is a prize to get',
        'B You give them the address of your friend to make them a surprise',
        'C You verify if the email is reliable and decide upon it with your',
        'D You answer the email'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'C You verify if the email is reliable and decide upon it with your',
      explanation: 'You verify if the email is reliable and decide upon it with your',
    }
  ];

  public static dumpQuestions: Question3[] = [];
}
